http://www.swissturn.com/privacy-policy/

What We DoPrecision Machined ProductsWhy Swiss?EngineeringQualityFacilitiesWho We ServeWho We AreCompany HistoryTeamEmployee – OwnersNewsContact UsRequest a QuoteWhat You NeedISO CertificateTerms & Conditions of SaleRegulatory StatementsTerms & Conditions of PurchaseSwissturn USA respects your right to privacy.This privacy policy sets out how Swissturn USA uses and protects any information that you give Swissturn USA when you use this website. Swissturn USA is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Swissturn USA may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 01-01-2017.WHAT WE COLLECTWe may collect the following information:– name and job title – contact information including email address – demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests – other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offersWHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHERWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:– Internal record keeping. – We may use the information to improve our products and services. – We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. – From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITESOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Terms & Conditions of SaleDriving DirectionsRegulatory InfoPress & News
Phone: : (508) 987-6211 |
Fax: (508) 987-9914© 2020 Swissturn. All Rights Reserved. | Privacy Policy | Sitemap
SwissturnWhat We DoPrecision Machined ProductsWhy Swiss?EngineeringQualityFacilities BackWho We ServeWho We AreCompany HistoryTeamEmployee – OwnersNews BackContact UsRequest a Quote BackWhat You NeedISO CertificateTerms & Conditions of SaleRegulatory StatementsTerms & Conditions of Purchase Back
× Close Panel
